simply mary here with the classic power
hitter and we are going to talk about
how we use this little gadget right here
so you are the one that controls the
delivery with this device
so here we go you're going to place the
doob right here
in this little tip and make sure it's
nice and snug so it does not fall
out so here's a demo you're going to
throw your thumb over this hole and
you're going to press
down and the smoke will come out the tip
but don't forget to move your thumb out
of the way before you let go
so you don't suck the dew back down in
there so you're going to keep it going
by
feeding it air just by squeezing it like
that and here we go with the real thing
you're going to place it in there make
sure it's tight light it
get it going nice and good put on the
cap and give it a squeeze to keep it
going and give it a little bit of air
and another squeeze to make sure you're
going good and
you're off it's that easy so you can
deliver
as little or as much smoke as you want
the biggest problem i have ever had with
this
was dropping a dupe down in there
they're extremely hard to get out if you
do that
so i really want to make it clear to
move your thumb out of the way before
you
you know release because you can suck
them back in there but that's the only
problem i've ever had other than that
it's my favorite tool
ever